programmingsimplified.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Programming Simplified

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/programmingsimplified.com).  

Privacy Policy for [www.programmingsimplified.com](http://www.programmingsimplified.com/)

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, we makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

The DoubleClick DART cookie

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

We use [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/) on our website to serve ads and cookies will be placed on your computer to improve ad serving.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our website and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
(Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

We use Amazon affiliate program to serve links and banners on our websites.
